<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CryptoMarket</string>
    <string name="news_1">Ripple appears to have acquired a brand-new partner. On LinkedIn, Punnoose Mathew, the managing director of Joyalukkas Exchange, which is based in Dubai, stated that he met with Mark Johnson, William Cooley, and Nick Taplin at Ripple, which is referred to as "the leader in blockchain and crypto solutions for enterprises." Matthew penned:\n\n<b>Joyalukkas Exchange Offers Fast and Easy Remittance to the Middle East</b>\n\nJoyalukkas Exchange is a subsidiary of the Joyalukkas Group, a global conglomerate worth multiple billions of dollars and a well-known jewelry trading brand. One of the leading providers of foreign exchange services in the region is the goal of the payment service provider. According to Joyalukkas Exchanges website, they provide a wide range of remittance solutions to each customer and guarantee the best rates for cross-border payments. In order to accomplish this, the provider of payment services has formed a number of partnerships that make it possible for "quick and easy transfers to any part of the world at the best rates." With the help of the instant money transfer service, money can be transferred in a matter of minutes by withdrawing it from an account or withdrawing it in cash from a variety of establishments in selected nations.\n\n<b>Western Union Partners with Joyalukkas Exchange to Offer XRP Payments</b>\n\nOne of Western Unions main agents is Joyalukkas Exchange. Customers can use it to send and receive money to over 200,000 agent locations around the world. Additionally, the service provider has collaborated with Transfast, Ezremit, and IME, three payment processors.</string>
    <string name="news_2">The Helium Foundation has proposed March 28, 2023 as the date for migrating data to the Solana network. The Solana network has high throughput and transaction scalability. After a 24-hour transition, Helium-based protocols, including digital wallets, will become available on the Solana network. Helium-based wallet users will be able to continue using their wallets backed by the original seed phrases.\n\nFollowing the announcement, Solanas price is up about 11.4% in the past 24 hours to trade at $26.45. In addition, the Helium network is an extensive blockchain with a market capitalization of around $411,518,421 and a 24-hour trading volume of around $7,943,483.\n\nWhile most Helium token holders do not need to take any action, HNT Whales are encouraged to work closely with developers to test certain features. For example, users of the original Helium Hotspot app are encouraged to upgrade to the new Helium Wallet app. Heliums current level 1 blockchain will be stopped 24 hours prior to data transfer as it will become a level 2 blockchain.</string>
    <string name="news_3">Leading fiat-crypto payment gateway Alchemy Pay has announced its support for Google Pay — allowing Android phone users to purchase crypto directly with their bank cards.\n\nFollowing the announcement, Alchemy Pays native token (ACH) surged up to a local high of $0.04 — recording a 67% gain in the last 24 hours.\n\nACH has sustained an uptrend in recent times — recording a 180% gain in the 7-day time frame and a cumulative of 270% over the last 30 days, according to CryptoSlate data.\n\n<b>Support for Google Pay</b>\n\nThe surge in ACH is linked to Alchemy Pays move to expand its reach of the mobile wallet market with the new support for Google Pay, according to a Feb. 20 announcement.\n\nAlchemy Pay had earlier inched support for Apple Pay, hence the support for Google Pay will allow iOS and Android phone users to easily purchase crypto via the app with their bank cards.\n\nOn Google Pay, Alchemy Pay will provide support for purchasing crypto using the following fiat currencies: USD, EUR, KRW, SGD, AUD, TWD, TRY, CAD, JPY, AED, NZD, and HKD.\n\nBeyond Google Pay and Apple Pay, Alchemy Pay also supports payments in Mastercard and Visa across 173 countries.</string>
    <string name="news_4">MakerDAO announced on Feb. 20 a long-awaited change to its GitHub operations.\n\n“We are now at a place where Dai Foundation has handed over the management of the MakerDAO Github organization to the TechOps Core Unit, hoping to reduce bureaucracy and to move Dai Foundation a step further away from day-to-day operational tasks.”\n\nThe move comes after the Dai Foundation called for a provisional change to its software development services and overall GitHub management in its Q1 2022 report.\n\nBefore that — during the dissolution of the Maker Foundation in 2021 — the Dai Foundation assumed temporary caretaking responsibilities for the MakerDAO Github repository.\n\n<b>How the changes relate to assets</b>\n\nBefore transferring the operational aspects to a new party, the Dai Foundation undertook a comprehensive cleanup and reclassification effort of the MakerDAO`s GitHub.\n\nHowever, the organization’s mandate did not extend to providing software development nor operational services, rather it was to provide assurance of intellectual property ownership.\n\nIt did so along with the introduction of new tools and processes to simplify the transfer of copyright for any new protocol software and related content to the Dai Foundation — a process that is now complete, the foundation states.\n\nAs per the upgrade, TechOps Core Unit will ensure read access for all to the software that is used in both Maker Project and MakerDAO. It will also ensure that all public repositories use a license, and that public content managers are advised on copy right information from the Dai Foundation.\n\nA full list of the agreed upon details can be found on the MakerDAO forum.</string>
    <string name="news_5">FTX Japan will restart withdrawal services for fiat and crypto assets as of noon local time on Feb. 21, the company said in an announcement made Monday.\n\nThe announcement meets a promise made in December by the exchange, whose assets in the country were largely ring-fenced under Japanese law.\n\n“Due to the large number of requests from customers, it may take some time for the withdrawal process to be completed,” the company said in a statement. “We will announce the resumption of other FTX Japan services as soon as possible.”\n\nThe Japanese exchange shuttered Nov. 8, a few days before FTX as a whole filed for bankruptcy in the U.S. The Japanese unit, alongside FTX Europe, has been earmarked for an early sale as the estate attempts to recoup funds.</string>
    <string name="news_6">Animoca Brands, a web3 investor focused on gaming and metaverse, invested an undisclosed amount in EthSign, a decentralized electronic signature platform.\n\nThe investment will help EthSign continue building its token management platform called TokenTable and launch it publicly, EthSign said Monday. TokenTable is currently live in beta and allows users to manage the issuance and distribution of tokens.\n\nWhile the investment amount wasn`t disclosed, EthSign co-founder Potter Li told The Block that the firm`s total funding to date now stands at $14 million. Since EthSign has previously raised $12.65 million in two funding rounds, that would suggest Animoca invested $1.35 million in the company. Animoca Brands declined to comment on the size of the investment.\n\n<b>TokenTable goes live</b>\n\nEthSign`s TokenTable went live last week in beta. It lets web3 founders, investors and employees manage token holdings on chain.\n\nThe current token management process is tedious, according to EthSign. Founders have to manually distribute and track token allocations, while investors and employees have to keep track of dates of token unlocks, it said. TokenTable, on the other hand, leverages blockchain technology for record-keeping, fund transfer and agreement enforcement, EthSign said.\n\n"TokenTable puts terms of legal agreements into the smart contract, thereby ensuring that the investment terms of every agreement signed on the platform are executed — this is a major step in bolstering the rule of law with the rule of code," according to EthSign.\n\nAnimoca Brands itself seeks to benefit from TokenTable, being an investor in more than 380 firms and a frequent recipient of token allocations.\n\n"Many projects use excel spreadsheets to calculate and track token allocation and unlocking, which is inefficient, not secure, and highly inconvenient," Yat Siu, co-founder and chairman of Animoca Brands, said in a statement. "EthSign`s TokenTable addresses these challenges to enable a new standard of operational efficiency for web3 businesses."</string>
    <string name="news_7">The foundation behind the Klaytn blockchain has introduced a number of changes aimed at increasing the transparency and sustainability of the network. Leading South Korean layer 1 blockchain has announced a new governance system and updated tokenomics proposal to expand the technical capabilities of the Klaytn ecosystem.\n\nThe Klaytn Foundation is set to propose a comprehensive agenda to the governance council that sets out a blockchain roadmap for 2023 and beyond. The agenda will be proposed before the council vote, which will take place between February 22 and February 28. It will include details of the new governance system and an updated tokenomics proposal.\n\n<b>Sangmin Seo</b>, Representative Director of Klaytn Foundation, said:\n\n“With our new initiatives, the Klaytn blockchain has an opportunity to take yet another step towards decentralization. The Foundation remains steadfast in its commitment to advancing blockchain technology, fostering community trust, and relentlessly working toward decentralization.”</string>
</resources>